quiltropolis.net 2015-10-29

# Quiltropolis Quilting Newsletter

## Privacy Policy:

Quiltropolis is committed to protecting your privacy and any information you share with us.

We may collect personal information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register, or subscribe to our newsletter. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, or phone number. We will collect personal information only if it is voluntarily submitted.

**We keep all customer information confidential and do not share or sell any information with any outside parties.**

****Our site uses "cookies" in some cases to maintain your session. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes. A user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Quiltropolis collects and uses user information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve our Site_  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To improve customer service_  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * _To administer a content, promotion, survey or other site feature_  
To send users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _To send periodic emails_  
The email address users provide during registration may be used to ask them questions, respond to their inquiries or send updates pertaining to their registration. If a user decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include new products, updates, related product or site information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe links at the bottom of each email.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect your personal information. This includes contracting reputable third parties to monitor the security of our site and data.

Sensitive and private information transferred between the site and users happen over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for users.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

Our privacy policy may be updated at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

_Our privacy policy was last updated on February 1, 2014._
